[
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to the manmade Fort Peck Lake?",
        "answer": "Montana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lake Winnipesaukee is the largest lake in which US state?",
        "answer": "New Hampshire"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two `Great` lakes are the largest two lakes entirely within Canada?",
        "answer": "Great Bear and Great Slave lakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Croatia? ",
        "answer": "Zagreb "
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do `Yoopers` live?",
        "answer": "Michigan`s Upper Peninsula"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country is the Bataan Peninsula?",
        "answer": "The Philippines"
    },
    {
        "question": "One of the Midwest`s `Quad Cities` is named for what three-mile-long island in the Mississippi?",
        "answer": "Rock Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "Utah`s Great Salt Lake is the largest remnant of what enormous prehistoric lake?",
        "answer": "Lake Bonneville"
    },
    {
        "question": "The world`s least salty seawater is found in the Gulf of Bothnia, between what two countries?",
        "answer": "Sweden and Finland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Parisian hill is home to the Moulin Rouge and the Sacr\u00e9-C\u0153ur Basilica?",
        "answer": "Montmartre"
    },
    {
        "question": "What desert is home to the Ahaggar and Tibesti mountains?",
        "answer": "Sahara"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is considered the waterfall capital of Canada?",
        "answer": "Hamilton"
    },
    {
        "question": "What lake was created when the Bagnell Dam was built across the Osage River?",
        "answer": "Lake of the Ozarks"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official state tree of California?",
        "answer": "California Redwood"
    },
    {
        "question": "Death Valley is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cheyenne is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "Wyoming"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Vatican owns a telescope in what U.S. state?",
        "answer": "Arizona"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lei Day is a special May Day celebration held in which of America`s states?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city in the U.S. is home to the National Mustard Museum?",
        "answer": "Middleton, Wisconsin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Off what country are the islands of Islay, Mull, and St. Kilda located?",
        "answer": "Scotland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Catalonia is a region of what country?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Rungnado 1st of May Stadium, built in honor of the May Day holiday, exists in which country?",
        "answer": "North Korea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Christmas Island is a territory of what country?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "The nearest permanently inhabited place to the North Pole is part of which country?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Santa`s postal code in Canada?",
        "answer": "H0H 0H0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ocean is Christmas Island located in?",
        "answer": "Indian Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which Canadian province would you find Christmas Island?",
        "answer": "Nova Scotia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Candy canes are said to have originated from which European country?",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "Most of Transylvania is now part of what modern-day country?",
        "answer": "Romania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Niagara Falls is located between which two Great Lakes?",
        "answer": "Lake Erie and Lake Ontario -- The Niagara River feeds three waterfalls -- American Falls and Bridal Veil Falls on the U.S. side and Horseshoe Falls on the Canadian side."
    },
    {
        "question": "Moraine Lake is a glacially fed, turquoise body of water found where?",
        "answer": "Canadian Rockies -- Lacated in Banff National Park, the lake is over 6,000 feet above sea level, within the Valley of the Ten Peaks in Alberta, Canada."
    },
    {
        "question": "What makes the water in Australia`s Hutt Lagoon appear bright pink?",
        "answer": "Algae -- The lake`s pink Pepto-Bismol-like coloring comes from a naturally occurring, carotenoid-producing algae that is a great source of Vitamin A."
    },
    {
        "question": "Lake Bled in Slovenia features a picturesque island famous for its what?",
        "answer": "Historic church -- It dates back to the 17th century. Parts of the church are older, however, with frescoes dated to 1470. Its 171-foot tower can be seen from the lakeshore."
    },
    {
        "question": "Mount Elbrus is the highest mountain in which country?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In France, what would you buy in a Boulangerie?",
        "answer": "Bread"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state is `The Gopher State`?",
        "answer": "Minnesota"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which African country is Lilongwe the capital of?",
        "answer": "Malawi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed `Keystone state`?",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bismarck is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "North Dakota"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Michigan?",
        "answer": "Lansing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which African capital city is named from the Greek meaning of `three towns`?",
        "answer": "Tripoli"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the Commandaria wine region?",
        "answer": "Cyprus"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Gobi Desert lies within which two countries?",
        "answer": "China and Mongolia"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Bunya Pine tree is native to which country?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nation`s legislative body is named The Riksdag?",
        "answer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nation`s legislative body is named The Eduskunta?",
        "answer": "Finland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is Chicago in?",
        "answer": "Illinois"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which desert covers part of China and Mongolia?",
        "answer": "Gobi"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the Taj Mahal?",
        "answer": "Agra"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two states border Lake Champlain?",
        "answer": "New York and Vermont"
    }
]